Benjamin Spock and Mary Morgan Papers
Benjamin Spock and Mary Morgan Papers
- Correspondence-subject files
  - Casady, Simon (Box 167)
  - Case Western Reserve University, See Western Reserve University.
  - Castro Ruiz, Fidel (Box 167)
  - Catholic Press Association (Box 167)
  - Catholic School Board, Diocese of Pittsburgh Special Education Department (Box 167)
  - CBS News (Box 167)
  - Cedar Cross College (Box 167)
  - CEL Communications, Inc., 2 folders (Box 168)
  - Center for Attitudinal Healing (Box 168)
  - Center for Constitutional Rights (Box 168)
  - Center for Defense Information (Box 168)
  - The Center for Effective Discipline (Box 168)
  - Center for International Policy (Box 168)
  - Center for International Visitors of Greater Boston (Box 168)
  - Center for Science in the Public Interest (Box 168)
  - Center for the Study of Contemporary Belief (Box 168)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions (Box 168)
  - Center for the Study of Education and Politics, Inc., Middletown, CT (Box 168)
  - Center for the Study of Psychiatry, Inc. (Box 168)
  - Center for War/Peace Studies (Box 168)
  - Central Arkansas Agency on Aging, Inc. (Box 168)
  - Central Committee for Conscientious Objectors (Box 168)
  - Central Massachusetts Safe Energy Project, Inc. (Box 168)
  - Central Michigan University (Box 168)
  - Central Neuropsychiatric Association (Box 168)
  - CFCF Radio, Montreal (Box 168)
  - CFRB Radio, Toronto (Box 168)
  - CFTO-TV Limited, Toronto (Box 168)
  - Chacko, Rose (Box 168)
  - Chaplin, Charlie (Box 168)
  - Chapman, Robert C. (Box 168)
  - Charlotte (NC) Observer (Box 168)
  - Charlotte-Mecklenburg Schools, Charlotte, NC (Box 168)
  - Charter Group for a Pledge of Conscience (Box 168)
  - Cherry Hill High School West, Cherry Hill, NJ (Box 168)
  - Chessler, Sey (Box 168)
  - Chevalier, Victor (Box 168)
  - Chicago, Judy (Box 168)
  - Chicago Public Schools Controversy (Box 168)
  - Chicago Sun-Times (Box 168)
  - Chicago's American (Box 168)
  - Child Development Center, New York, NY (Box 169)
  - Child Development Group of Mississipps (Box 169)
  - Child rearing study, 1960-1981; 7 folders (Box 169)
  - Child rearing study [cont.], 1982-1994; undated; 8 folders (Box 170)
  - Child Study Association of America, 2 folders (Box 171)
  - Child Welfare League of America (Box 171)
  - Childbirth Without Pain Education Association (Box 171)
  - The Childhood Project, Inc. (Box 171)
  - The Children and Divorce Resource Network (Box 171)
  - Children in Crisis Conference, New York, NY (Box 171)
  - Children of War Tour (Box 171)
  - Children's Campaign for Nuclear Disarmament (Box 171)
  - Children's Defense Fund, See Edelman, Marian Wright.
  - Children's Express (Box 171)
  - The Children's Hospital, Buffalo, NY (Box 171)
  - The Children's Hospital Medical Center, Boston, MA (Box 171)
  - Children's Hospital of Michigan, Detroit, MI (Box 171)
  - Children's Hospital of Orange County, Orange, CA (Box 171)
  - The Children's Hospital of Philadelphia (Box 171)
  - Children's Institute International (Box 172)
  - The Children's Journal (Box 172)
  - The Children's Medical Center of New York (Box 172)
  - Children's Mental Health Center, Columbus, OH (Box 172)
  - Children's Peace Petition (Box 172)
  - Children's Rights of New York (Box 172)
  - Children's School of Science, Woods Hole, MA (Box 172)
  - Chile Action Group (Box 172)
  - Chiles, Lawton (Box 172)
  - China, 2 folders (Box 172)
  - Choi, Tohshik (Box 172)
  - Chomsky, Noam (Box 172)
  - Chopra, Depak, 2 folders (Box 172)
  - Christian Herald (Box 172)
  - Christian Interfaith Party (Box 172)
  - Christian Medical College Hospital, Vellore, South India (Box 172)
  - The Christophers (Box 172)
  - Chumak, Peter, 2 folders (Box 173)
  - The Chunichi Shimbun (Box 173)
  - Church, Frank (Box 173)
  - The Church Federation of Greater Chicago (Box 173)
  - Cincinnati Action for Peace (Box 173)
  - Cipriš, Željko (Box 173)
  - Circumcision, 2 folders (Box 173)
  - Citizen Diplomacy. Inc. (Box 173)
  - Citizens' Action for Safe Energy, Inc. (Box 173)
  - Citizens Committee for Constitutional Liberties (Box 173)
  - Citizens Committee for Effective Education (Box 173)
  - Citizens' Committee for Julian Bond (Box 173)
  - Citizens Crusade Against Poverty (Box 173)
  - Citizens Crusade Against Poverty, 2 folders (Box 174)
  - Citizens for a Vote on Vietnam (Box 174)
  - Citizens for Decent Literature (Box 174)
  - Citizens Energy Project (Box 174)
  - Citizens for the President's Education Program (Box 174)
  - Citizens' Forum, Chicago, IL (Box 174)
  - The Citizens Party (Box 174)
  - Citizens to Defeat (OH) State Issue No. 2 (Box 174)
  - The City Club, Cleveland, OH (Box 174)
  - City Club of Rochester (NY) (Box 174)
  - City of Cleveland (Box 174)
  - City of New York Department of Correction (Box 174)
  - The Civil Liberties Legal Defense Fund, Inc., 3 folders (Box 174)
  - CKWS Toronto (Box 174)
  - Clamshell Alliance (Box 174)
  - Clamshell Alliance (Box 175)
  - Clark, Dick (Box 175)
  - Clark, Dick (Box 175)
    Gift of Kathy Clark, 2020.
  - Clark, Grenville (Box 175)
  - Clark, Joseph S. (Box 175)
  - Clark, Margaret (Box 175)
  - Clark, Ramsey (Box 175)
  - Clark, Sheldon D. (Box 175)
  - Clarkson N. Potter, Inc./Publisher (Box 175)
  - ¡Claro! Central Latin American Relief Organization, See Hoffman, Abbott Howard "Abbie".
  - Clemens, Cyril (Box 175)
  - Clement, Kenneth W. (Box 175)
  - Clergy and Laity Concerned (Box 175)
  - Cleveland Academy of Medicine (Box 175)
  - Cleveland (OH) Area Peace/Action Council (Box 175)
  - Cleveland Child Rearing Study, See Child rearing study.
  - Cleveland Committee for UNICEF, See United States Committee for UNICEF. (Box 175)
  - Cleveland Committee to End the War in Vietnam (Box 175)
  - Cleveland Dental Society (Box 175)
  - Cleveland Heights (OH) City Council (Box 175)
  - The Cleveland Medical Library Association (Box 176)
  - Cleveland Metropolitan General Hospital (Box 176)
  - The Cleveland Psychoanalytic Society (Box 176)
  - Cleveland Public Schools (Box 176)
  - Cleveland Tutorial Project (Box 176)
  - Clifford W. Beers Guidance Clinic, New Haven, CT (Box 176)
  - Clinical Pediatrics (Box 176)
  - Clinton, William Jefferson (Bill) and Hillary Rodham, 2 folders (Box 176)
  - Coalition for Alternatives to Shearon Harris (CASH), Durham, NC (Box 176)
  - Coalition for Direct Action at Seabrook (Box 176)
  - Coalition on the Economic Crisis (Box 176)
  - Coalition to Free South Vietnamese Political Prisoners (Box 176)
  - The Coalition for International Cooperation and Peace (Box 176)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (Box 176)
  - Coalition for a National Health Service (Box 176)
  - Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy (Box 176)
  - Coalition for a Non-Nuclear World (Box 176)
  - Coalition for a People's Alternative (Box 176)
  - Coastal Mountain Land Trust, Rockport, ME (Box 177)
  - Cobble Hill Press (Box 177)
  - Cochrane, William M. (Box 177)
  - Coffin, Tristram (Box 177)
  - Coffin, William Sloane, Jr. (Box 177)
  - Cohelan, Jeffrey (Box 177)
  - Cohen, Alexander H. (Box 177)
  - Cohen, William (Box 177)
  - Cole, Maria Hawkins (Mrs. Nat King Cole) (Box 177)
  - Coleman, Lester L. (Box 177)
  - Coleman Advocates for Children & Youth, San Francisco, CA (Box 177)
  - Coles, Robert (Box 177)
  - College of Mount St Joseph on the Ohio (Box 177)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. (CBS) (Box 177)
    See also CBS News.
  - Columbia (University) Daily Spectator (Box 177)
  - Columbia Records (Box 177)
  - Columbia University (Box 177)
  - Commager, Henry Steele (Box 177)
  - Comité Moratoire du Vietnam (Box 177)
  - Commission on the Needs of Women (Box 177)
  - Committee for Artistic and Intellectual Freedom in Iran, See Hogue, Grady C.
  - Committee for Democratic Election Laws (Box 177)
  - Committee for a Direct Attack on the Vietnam War (Box 177)
  - Committee for Health Rights in Central America (CHRICA) (Box 177)
  - Committee for a Humane Abortion Law (Box 177)
  - Committee for May 10th Demonstration (Box 177)
  - Committee for a National Health Service (Box 177)
  - Committee for Nonviolent Action (Box 177)
  - Committee for Nuclear Information (Box 177)
  - Committee for Nuclear Responsibility, Inc. (Box 177)
  - Committee for Puerto Rican Decolonization (Box 177)
  - Committee for the Suit Against Government Misconduct (Box 177)
  - Committee of 100 Million to Impeach Lyndon B. Johnson (Box 177)
  - Committee of 1000 (Box 177)
  - The Committee of Responsibility, Inc., 2 folders (Box 178)
  - Committee of the Professions (Box 178)
  - Committee on Psychological Effects of the Nuclear Age (Box 178)
  - Committee on Social Security for Physicians (Box 178)
  - Committee to Aid the Bloomington Students (Box 178)
  - Committee to Aid the Debs, Hall Defendants (Box 178)
  - Committee to Defend the French Students (Box 178)
  - Committee to Defend Iowa Students (Box 178)
  - Committee to Defend Poor and Working People Against Oppression (Box 178)
  - Committee to Defend the Rights of PFC Howard Petrick (Box 178)
  - The Committee to End Radiological Hazards (Box 178)
  - Committee to Free the Mao Tsetung Defendants (Box 178)
  - Committee to Protect Our Children's Teeth, Inc. (Box 178)
  - Committee to Save OSHA (Box 178)
  - Committee to Save Our Children's Minds (Box 178)
  - Commoner, Barry (Box 178)
  - Commonweal (Box 178)
  - Commonwealth Club of California (Box 178)
  - Communication Research Institute, Miami, FL (Box 178)
  - Communications Research Machines, Inc. Consumer Division (Box 178)
  - Communist Party, U.S.A. (Box 178)
  - The Communitarians of the Community Church of New York, New York, NY (Box 178)
  - Community Action for Youth, Inc., Cleveland, OH (Box 178)
  - The Community Church of Boston (Box 178)
  - Community for Creative Non-Violence (Box 179)
  - Community Health Foundation, Cleveland, OH (Box 179)
  - Community Mental Health (Box 179)
  - The Comstock Club, Inc., Sacramento, CA (Box 179)
  - Concern (Box 179)
  - Concerned Mothers' Coalition (Box 179)
  - The Conference on Socialism and Activism (Box 179)
  - Congress of Racial Equality (Box 179)
  - Conscience & Military Tax Campaign (Box 179)
  - Consider the Alternatives (Box 179)
  - Consumer Commission on the Accreditation of Health Services, Inc. (Box 179)
  - Consumer Reports (Box 179)
  - Consumers Union of U.S., Inc. (Box 179)
  - Contact (Box 179)
  - Contemporary Books (Box 179)
  - Conyers, John (Box 179)
  - Cook, Robert M. (Box 179)
  - Cooke, Goodwin (Box 179)
  - Cooper, John Sherman (Box 179)
  - The Cooper Union (Box 179)
  - Copeland, Edward (Box 179)
  - The Cornelian Corner (Box 179)
  - Cortlandt Forum (Box 179)
  - Cosmopolitan (Box 179)
  - Costanza, Margaret (Box 179)
  - Council for a Livable World (Box 180)
  - Council for Basic Education (Box 180)
  - Council on Economic Priorities (Box 180)
  - Council for Exceptional Children, Willowdale, ON (Box 180)
  - The Council on Interracial Books for Children, Inc. (Box 180)
  - Council for International Exchange of Scholars (Box 180)
  - Council of State Governments (Box 180)
  - Councille, Clifford, See Family correspondence.
  - Councille, Virginia "Ginger", See Family correspondence.
  - County Government (Box 180)
  - County Hospital Progress Committee, Cleveland, OH (Box 180)
  - Cousins, Norman (Box 180)
  - Covarrubias, Juan (Box 180)
  - Cox, Donald William (Box 180)
  - Cranston, Alan (Box 180)
  - Cravens, Liz (Box 180)
  - Crawdad Alliance, St. Louis, MO (Box 180)
  - Crawford, Kenneth G. (Box 180)
  - Creative Playthings. Inc., Herndon, PA (Box 180)
  - Creative Television, Inc. (Box 180)
  - Critical Mass Energy Project (Box 180)
  - Croll, Theodore, P., 3 folders (Box 180)
  - Croll, Theodore, P. (Box 181)
  - Crow Dog, Leonard (Box 181)
  - Crown Publishers, Inc. (Box 181)
  - Cryer, Gretchen (Box 181)
  - Csikszentmihalyi, Mihalyi (Box 181)
  - CTV Television Network, Ltd. Toronto, ON (Box 181)
  - Cuba, 1975; 1993; 6 folders (Box 181)
  - Cuba, 1993-2000; 7 folders (Box 182)
  - Cuba, 2002; 2 folders (Box 183)
  - Current (Box 183)
  - Curtis, Dock (Box 183)
  - Curtis Publishing Company (Box 183)
  - Curtiss, Paul H. (Box 183)
  - Cushing Academy, Ashburnham, MA (Box 183)
  - Cuu Quoc Weekly Hanoi (Box 183)
  - The D.C. Nine (Box 183)
  - D.C. Statehood Party (Box 183)
  - Dahl, Robert (Box 183)
  - Daley, William R. (Box 183)
  - Damerell, V.R. (Box 183)
  - Danbury Hospital, Danbury, CT (Box 183)
  - Darrow, Daniel Cody (Box 183)
  - Dartmouth Medical School (Box 183)
  - Dartmouth Student Forum (Box 183)
  - Davidson, James Alfred (Box 183)
  - Davis, Angela (Box 183)
  - Davis, Ossie (Box 183)
  - Day, Jack G. (Box 183)
  - Day Care (Box 183)
  - Dayton (OH) Women's Liberation (Box 183)
  - De Anza College, Cupertino, CA (Box 183)
  - Declaration of Scholars and Professionals Concerned About, U.S. War Crimes in Indochina (Box 183)
  - DeCrow, Karen (Box 183)
  - Dee, Ruby, See Black Academy of Arts and Letters, Inc.
  - Delacorte Press, 2 folders (Box 184)
  - Delamater, Eugene (Box 552)
  - Delaney, Michael (Box 552)
  - Delicious! (Box 184)
  - Dell Publishing (Box 184)
  - Dellinger, David (Box 184)
    See also Liberation.
  - Dellums, Ronald V. (Box 184)
  - Democratic National Committee (DNC) (Box 184)
  - Democratic Republic of Vietnam (Box 184)
  - Dennison, E. Allen (Box 184)
  - Denver, John (Box 184)
  - Devine, Samuel L. (Box 184)
  - Di Salle, Michael V. (Box 184)
  - Díaz Ordaz, Gustavo (Box 184)
  - The Dick Clark Company, Inc. (Box 184)
  - Dickerson, Carrie (Box 184)
  - Dickerson, Margaret (Box 184)
  - Dickinson College, Carlisle, PA (Box 184)
  - Dimowo, Emmanuel Abogunde (Box 184)
  - Direction 80 (Box 184)
  - Dirksen, Everett M. (Box 184)
  - The Disney Channel, See Walt Disney Television.
  - Dissent (Box 184)
  - Distributive Workers of America (Box 184)
  - Dixon, Suzanne (Box 184)
  - Doan, Gilbert E. (Box 184)
  - Doan School, Cleveland, OH (Box 184)
  - Dobrynin, Anatoly (Box 185)
  - The Documentary Guild (Box 185)
  - Dodd, Thomas J. (Box 185)
  - Dogramaci, Ishan (Box 185)
  - Dogwood Alliance (Box 185)
  - Dominick, Peter H. (Box 185)
  - Donnell, Lloyd Hamilton (Box 185)
  - Doubleday & Company, Inc. (Box 185)
  - Douglas, Melvyn (Box 185)
  - Douglas, Paul H. (Box 185)
  - Dove Letters (Box 185)
  - Dow, John G. (Box 185)
  - Down East (Box 185)
  - Draft Resisters Defense Fund, San Diego, CA (Box 185)
  - Dratch, Howard (Box 185)
  - Drew Associates, Inc., New York, NY (Box 185)
  - Drogin, Marc (Box 185)
  - The Drummer (Box 185)
  - Drye, Robert C., 2 folders (Box 185)
  - The Dublin Conference Group (Box 185)
  - Duca, Alfred M. (Box 185)
  - Duck, Linda (Box 185)
  - Duell, Sloan & Pearce, Inc., 1945-1965; 3 folders (Box 186)
  - Dunne, Emmaline B. (Box 186)
  - Dutton Childrens' Books (Box 186)
  - Dyer, Wayne W. (Box 186)
  - E. P. Dutton (Box 186)
  - Eager, Walter J. (Box 186)
  - Eagleton, Thomas F. (Box 186)
  - The Ealing Corporation (Box 186)
  - Earth Environment University, Otsu, Japan (Box 186)
  - East Junior High School, Superior, WI (Box 186)
  - East Pakistan Emergency Refugee Fund (Box 186)
  - East Stroudsburg State College (Box 186)
  - East/West Foundation, Boston, MA (Box 186)
  - East/ West Network (Box 186)
  - Eaton, Cyrus S. (Box 186)
  - Eaton, Joseph W. (Box 186)
  - Ebony (Box 186)
  - Ecocenter, Inc., Fayetteville, AR (Box 186)
  - Edelman, Marian Wright (Box 186)
  - Edelman International Corporation (Box 186)
  - Editions Elsevier Sequoia (Box 186)
  - Editions Québec/Amérique (Box 186)
  - Education/Action Conference on U.S. Crimes of War (Box 186)
  - The Education Digest (Box 187)
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (Box 187)
  - Educational Consulting Center, Westport, CT (Box 187)
  - Educators for Johnson and Humphrey (Box 187)
  - Edwards, Don (Box 187)
  - Eglash, Albert (Box 187)
  - Einstein, Albert, See Estate of Albert Einstein.
  - Eisenberg, Howard (Box 187)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Box 187)
  - El Modena High School, Orange, CA (Box 187)
  - El Salvador (Box 187)
  - The Elder (Box 187)
  - Elders, Joycelyn
  - Eldridge Cleaver for President Fund (Box 187)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Memorial Foundation (Box 187)
  - Elfenbein, Paul (Box 187)
  - Ellender, Allen, J. (Box 187)
  - Elliot & Elliot Architecture (Box 187)
  - Elsbree, Betty (Box 187)
  - Embassy of Iran (Box 187)
  - The Emereti Census (Box 187)
  - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee (Box 187)
    See also National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee.
  - Emergency Committee for a National Mobilization Against Racism (Box 187)
  - Emerson, Haven (Box 187)
  - Encampment for Citizenship (Box 187)
  - The End Hunger Network (Box 187)
  - End the Arms Race Coalition (Box 187)
  - Energy Policy Information Center (EPIC), also known as Energy Policy Information Institute; 2 folders (Box 187)
  - Energy Policy Information Center (EPIC) (Box 188)
  - England 1970 (Box 188)
  - Entelechy Press (Box 188)
  - Enterpoint Foundation (Box 188)
  - Environmental Action Foundation (Box 188)
  - Environmental Defense Fund (Box 188)
  - Environmental Education Group (Box 188)
  - Environmental Health Network (Box 188)
  - Environmental Policy Center (Box 188)
  - Epstein, Stephen, 2 folders (Box 552)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (ERA) (Box 188)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (ERA), 7 folders (Box 189)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (ERA), 2 folders (Box 190)
  - Erikson, Erik (Box 190)
  - Escalona, Sibylle K. (Box 190)
  - Esdaile, Robert (Box 190)
  - Esman, Aaron H. (Box 190)
  - Esquire (Box 190)
  - Esselstyn, Caldwell B.,Sr. (Box 190)
  - Estate of Albert Einstein (Box 190)
  - Evans, Eleanor Vishno (Box 190)
  - Evans House, Philadelphia, PA (Box 190)
  - Evanston (IL) Mental Health Society (Box 190)
  - Evenflo (Box 190)
  - The Evening and Sunday Bulletin, Philadelphia, PA (Box 190)
  - Excerpta Medica Foundation (Box 190)
  - The Executive Council of the Episcopal Church: Division of Radio and Television (Box 190)
  - Eyster, Richard H. (Box 190)
  - Fact Magazine, Inc. (Box 191)
  - Fahnestock, Karol (Box 191)
  - Fair Lawn (NJ) Committee for Peace in Vietnam (Box 191)
  - Fairleigh Dickinson University (Box 191)
  - Fallaci, Oriana (Box 191)
  - Families (Box 191)
  - Family Circle (Box 191)
  - Family Concern (Box 191)
  - Family Development Resources, Inc. (Box 191)
  - Family Journal (Box 191)
  - Family Learning (Box 191)
  - Farm Animal Reform Movement (FARM) (Box 191)
  - Farragut, Thomas J. III (Box 191)
  - Fascell, Dante B. (Box 191)
  - Fast To Save A People (Box 191)
  - Faulkner, Robert (Box 191)
  - Fawcett Publications, Inc. (Box 191)
  - Feder, Donald (Box 191)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), See United States Department of Justice, Federal Bureau of Investigation.
  - Federally Employed Women, Inc., Fort Knox, KY (Box 191)
  - Federation of American Scientists (Box 191)
  - Feinberg, Abraham L. (Box 191)
  - Feliciano, Carlos (Box 191)
  - Fell, Nicole (Box 191)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation (Box 191)
  - Feminist Anti-Nuclear Task Force of The Mobilization for Survival (Box 191)
  - The Feminist Majority Foundation (Box 191)
  - The Feminist Press Collective (Box 191)
  - Feurst, Robert (Box 191)
  - Fielding Institute (Box 191)
  - Fielding, William J. (Box 191)
  - Fifth Avenue Peace Parade Committee (Box 191)
  - Film News Now Foundation (Box 191)
  - Findlay College (Box 191)
  - Fingerprinting Children (Box 191)
  - Firing Line with William F. Buckley (Box 191)
  - First Congregational Church, Fall River, MA (Box 191)
  - The First Unitarian Church of Columbus, OH (Box 191)
  - Fishman, Leslie (Box 191)
  - Flanzer, Sally M. (Box 191)
  - Fleming, Anne (Box 192)
  - Fleming, Karl (Box 192)
  - Flippin (AR) Public Schools (Box 192)
  - Florida Coalition for Peace and Justice (Box 192)
  - Fluoridation, 1957-1980; correspondence; 4 folders (Box 192)
  - Fluoridation, articles and statements; 2 folders (Box 192)
  - Focus On Youth (Box 192)
  - Fogarty, John J. (Box 192)
  - Fonda, Jane (Box 192)
  - Food for Peace Program (Box 193)
  - Forand, Aime J. (Box 193)
  - Ford Clemency Program (Box 193)
  - The Ford Foundation (Box 193)
  - Ford, Gerald R. and Betty (Box 193)
  - The Ford Hall Forum, Boston, MA (Box 193)
  - Forslund, Scott (Box 193)
  - Fort Hood Three Defense Committee (Box 193)
  - Fortress Press, Philadelphia, PA (Box 193)
  - Foster Home Recruiting Center, Cleveland, OH (Box 193)
  - Foster Parenting (Box 193)
  - Foundation for Child Development (Box 193)
  - Foundation for New Social Directions (Box 193)
  - Fox, Dorothea, See Pocket Books, Inc.
  - Fraad, Lewis M. (Box 193)
  - Franklin Book Programs, Inc. (Box 193)
    See also Franklin Publications, Inc.
  - Franklin County (OH) Mental Health Association, Inc. (Box 193)
  - The Franklin Library (Box 193)
  - Franklin Publications, Inc. (Box 193)
    See also Franklin Book Programs, Inc.
  - Franklin Road Academy, Nashville, TN (Box 193)
  - Fraser, Donald M. (Box 193)
  - Fraser, Willard E. (Box 193)
  - Free South America (Box 193)
  - Free University, Amsterdam, Netherlands (Box 193)
  - The Freedom and Peace Party, See Peace and Freedom Party.
  - Freedom Now For Lt. Howe Committee, Denver, CO (Box 193)
  - Freedom Studies Center, Culpepper County, VA (Box 193)
  - Freeman, Leslie (Box 193)
  - Fremont-Smith, Frank (Box 193)
  - French Olympic Committee (Box 193)
  - Frente Unido Por Defensa Presos Politicos Puertorriqueños (Box 193)
  - Freud, Anna (Box 193)
  - Friedel, Samuel N. (Box 193)
  - Friedman, David (Box 193)
  - Friends Committee on National Legislation (Box 193)
  - Friends of the River (Box 193)
  - Friendship Press (Box 193)
  - Friendshipment :People-To-People Aid to Vietnam (Box 193)
  - Fromm, Erich (Box 194)
  - Frontier College (Canada) (Box 194)
  - FTA Louisville, KY (Box 194)
  - Fulbright, J. William (Box 194)
  - Full-Time Dads (Box 194)
  - Fuller, Buckminster (Box 194)
  - Fun, Travel, Adventure (Box 194)
  - The Fund for Education Concerning World Peace Through World Law (Box 194)
  - FUTURE (Folks United to Thwart Unsafe Radiation Emission) (Box 194)
  - Galbraith, John Kenneth (Box 194)
  - Gallagher, Wes (Box 194)
  - Gallaudet College (Box 194)
  - Gandhi, Indira (Box 194)
  - Gandhi Society for Human Rights, Inc. (Box 194)
  - Gardiner, Margaret (Box 194)
  - Gardner, Hy (Box 194)
  - Garr, Michael (Box 194)
  - Garvin, Charles E. (Box 194)
  - The Gazette and Daily, York, PA (Box 194)
  - Gentles, Ian (Box 194)
  - George Allen & Unwin, Ltd. (Box 194)
  - Georgia State University (Box 194)
  - Gerald Productions, Inc. (Box 194)
  - Gerber, Madge (Box 194)
  - Gerber, Magda (Box 194)
  - Gerrish, Edwin W. (Box 194)
  - Gesell Institute of Child Development, New Haven, CT (Box 194)
  - Gettysburg College, Gettysburg, PA (Box 194)
  - Ghelberg, Howard (Box 194)
  - GI Civil Liberties Defense Committee (Box 194)
  - Gilbert Linkous School, Blacksburg, VA (Box 194)
  - Ginsberg, Allen (Box 194)
  - Gjemre, Ken (Box 194)
  - Glassman, Norman (Box 194)
  - Glazer, Tom (Box 194)
  - Glendinning, Chellis (Box 194)
  - Glide Memorial Methodist Church, San Francisco, CA (Box 194)
  - Global Communications, Limited (Box 194)
  - Goldberg, Arthur J. (Box 194)
  - Goldberg, Ruth (Box 194)
  - Goldenson, Robert M. (Box 194)
  - Goldman, Gilbert (Box 194)
  - Goldwater, Barry (Box 195)
  - Goma Shobo, Inc., Tokyo, Japan (Box 195)
  - Gómez, Leonel (Box 195)
  - Good Housekeeping Magazine (Box 195)
  - Good Morning America (Box 195)
  - Good Samaritan Hospital and Medical Center, Portland, OR (Box 195)
  - Goodell, Charles (Box 195)
  - Goodwin, Richard N. (Box 195)
  - Gore, Albert (Box 195)
  - Gorman-Jacobs, Judy (Box 195)
  - Gottlieb, Sanford (Box 195)
  - Governor's Conference on Families, Little Rock, AR (Box 195)
  - Graaf, Vera (Box 195)